Guide to the Jimmy De Sana Papers 1954-1997 (bulk 1977-1990) MSS 202
© 2010 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Slides by project
  - Subseries D: $dobjects
    - Title: String, 1987 (Box 26)
      Description: String Abstraction shoot
      Number of Items: 63
    - Title:, 1986 (Box 26)
      Description: Ties and Roses shoot
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Tray
    - Title: (Box 26)
      Description: Tray with Vase
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Folded Paper
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations
      Number of Items: 19
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Drinking Glass
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Darrell Behind Glass
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Torn Green Paper
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Blue Geometric
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Blue Cellophane
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Clothes Pins
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Paper Doily
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Pennies
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Watermelon and Flour
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Description: Collage variations; Dalmation
    - Title: (Box 27)
      Number of Items: 178
  - Subseries E: Auto-Portrait
    - Title: Birds (Box 28)
      Description: Birds shoot
    - Title: (Box 28)
      Description: Burning Money
    - Title: (Box 28)
      Description: Cap
    - Title:, 1984 (Box 28)
      Description: Cellophane Tape
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 28)
      Description: Party Picks
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 28)
    - Title: (Box 28)
      Description: "Pizza Crust shoot "
      Number of Items: 136
    - Title:, 1984 (Box 28)
      Description: Play Money
    - Title:, 1985 (Box 28)
      Description: Smoke Cowboy
    - Title: (Box 28)
    - Title: (Box 28)
      Description: Male nude
  - Subseries F: Cut Up
    - Title: Pendant, 1985 (Box 29)
      Description: "Pendant "
    - Title:, 1985 (Box 29)
      Description: "Q tips "
    - Title: (Box 29)
      Description: Variations - Cut Piece
      Number of Items: 115
  - Subseries G: Salvation
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Gooseberries(deathless)
    - Title: (Box 30)
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Pear Collage
    - Title: (Box 30)
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Floral Arrangement
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Guitar
    - Title: (Box 30)
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: African Collage variations
    - Title: Sun God (Box 30)
    - Title: Sun God (Box 30)
    - Title: Burial Ceremony Mask (Box 30)
    - Title: Mirror (Box 30)
      Description: "Collage variations "
    - Title: Statue (Box 30)
    - Title: Two Flowers (Box 30)
    - Title: African Death Mask (Box 30)
    - Title: African Death Mask (Box 30)
    - Title: Shakers (Box 30)
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Collage Variations Torso
      Number of Items: 51
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Feet, Flowers, Powder
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Floral Arrangement Variations
      Number of Items: 60
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Artichoke Collage
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Twigs
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Household Protective Object
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: African Stick Figure
    - Title: (Box 30)
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Powder
      Number of Items: 34
    - Title: (Box 30)
    - Title: (Box 30)
      Description: Candle Sticks
    - Title: Statue with Pan (Box 31)
    - Title: Bird Mask (Box 31)
    - Title: (Box 31)
      Description: Branch
    - Title: Mask with Feathers (Box 31)
    - Title: (Box 31)
      Description: Coconut Collage
    - Title: Pom poms (Box 31)
    - Title: (Box 31)
      Description: "Collage variations Powder"
    - Title: African Statue (Box 31)
    - Title: (Box 31)
      Description: "Collage variations Gym shorts "
      Number of Items: 112
    - Title: (Box 31)
      Description: Parka shoot
    - Title: Tile (Box 31)
    - Title: Fruit (Box 31)
    - Title: Wings (Box 31)
    - Title: Intensive Care (Box 31)
    - Title: Flower Triptych (Box 31)
    - Title: Amaryllis (Box 31)
    - Title: Rose (Box 31)
    - Title: Carnation (Box 31)
    - Title: Flower (Box 31)
    - Title: Tile (Box 31)
    - Title: (Box 31)
    - Title: (Box 31)
- Series IV: Slides by theme
  - Subseries A: Documentation
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 32)
      Description: Bonlow Gallery Painting Show
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 32)
      Description: Painting - Marker Cones Documentation
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 32)
      Description: Painting - Athletic Tape Documentation
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 32)
      Description: Painting - Giant Beachball Documentation
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 32)
      Description: Painting - Sweatshirt Documentation
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 32)
      Description: Painting - Medusa Documentation
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 32)
      Description: Painting - Shaved Head Documentation
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 32)
      Description: Painting - Subject with Yellow Object Documentation
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 32)
      Description: Painting - Thimbles Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Q-Tips Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Rope Self-Portrait Documentation
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 32)
      Description: Oggi Domani Show
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Submission Documentation
      Process: 4x5 Color Transparency Slide
    - Title: (Box 32)
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Aluminum Foil Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Athletic Tape Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Auto Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Beachballs Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Bed Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Blow Up Doll Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Casters Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Chair Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Chocolate Syrup Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Coat Hanger Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Condom Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Contact Paper Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Storage Boxes Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Dishwasher Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Instant Camera Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Earring Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Egg Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Extension Cord Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Figure in bed with Lights Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Fur Coat Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Gauze Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Helmet Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Iguana Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Ladder Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Leaves Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Marker Cones Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Shoe Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Plastic Bags Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Pocketbook Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Pool Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Bottles Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Seashells and Eggshells Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Sweatshirt Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Toothpaste Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Travel Bags Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Tube Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Watermelon Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Party Picks Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Sofa Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Bubblegum Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Cowboy Hat Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Dalmation at Beach Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Pants Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Birds Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Cellophane Tape Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Pizza Crust Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Smoke Cowboy Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Crackers Docmentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Play Money Docmentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Early Work Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Landscape Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Portraits Documentation
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Number of Items: 62
    - Title: (Box 32)
      Description: Fellowship Application
      Process: Fellowship Application
    - Title: (Box 32)
  - Subseries B: Events
    - Title: (Box 33)
      Description: Bryant Park
      Number of Items: 78
    - Title: (Box 33)
      Description: Central Park
    - Title: (Box 33)
      Description: Events Theme
      Number of Items: 254
  - Subseries C: Altered Landscape
    - Title: (Box 34)
      Description: Shoot for Altered Landscapes
      Number of Items: 265
    - Title: (Box 35)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: "Darrell Bagley model Pipecleaner whiskers"
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Dog
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Feet
    - Title: (Box 36)
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Toys
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Clothing
    - Title: (Box 36)
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Jimmy Jr.
      Number of Items: 42
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Jimmy Jr. Polka Dot Dress
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Jimmy Jr. with Another Dalmation
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Magician's Hat
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Folder labeled “New York City in 1979: To Jeanne’s Insulted Beauty” text by Kathy Acker, images by JDS
    - Title: (Box 36)
      Description: Misc
      Number of Items: 142
  - Subseries E: O'Hara's Wife
    - Title: (Box 37)
      Description: Shots from the 1981 film with Jodie Foster and Edward Asner
      Number of Items: 552
  - Subseries F: Paper Collage
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: 1919 Part II
    - Title: Broken Ovals (Box 38)
      Description: Broken Ovals Collage Variations
    - Title: Broken Ovals (Box 38)
      Number of Items: 131
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: Seven Wonders Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: Bauhaus Collage Pt 1 Collage Variations
      Number of Items: 79
    - Title: Chair (Box 38)
    - Title: Chair (Box 38)
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: Oranges Collage variations
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: Stone Column Collage variations
      Number of Items: 53
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: Globe and Television
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: Globe Collage
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: Desire Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: Paper Collage
      Number of Items: 64
    - Title: (Box 38)
      Description: Pine Cones shoot
    - Title: (Box 39)
      Description: Collage Variations
      Number of Items: 211
    - Title: (Box 39)
      Description: Dinosaur
    - Title: Faith in the cosmos (Box 39)
    - Title: (Box 39)
      Description: ff oo uu
    - Title: (Box 39)
    - Title: (Box 39)
      Description: pas une artiste
    - Title: Forget Me Not (Box 39)
      Description: "Grid Crumpled Brown Paper"
    - Title: (Box 39)
      Description: Forget Me
    - Title: (Box 39)
      Description: Pour/Jamals Variations
    - Title: (Box 39)
    - Title: (Box 39)
    - Title: (Box 39)
      Description: Objects for Collage
    - Title: (Box 40)
      Description: Nude, Leaves, Collage
    - Title: (Box 40)
      Description: Gum Wrappers Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 40)
      Description: Helicopters Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 40)
      Description: Sanctity Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 40)
      Description: Cyrptogenic Collage
    - Title: (Box 40)
      Description: Shoe Laces Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 40)
      Description: Spirit Traps Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 40)
      Description: Dino for Collage
    - Title: (Box 40)
      Description: Toy Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 40)
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Facer Collage
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Pomegranate
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Wooden Object
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Pom Poms
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Gee Gaw Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: "Inna Churicova Cut up, inverse"
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: "Gleb Panfilov Cut up, inverse"
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Cynosure Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Sublime Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Enchantment Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Celestial Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Serenity Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Exhaltation Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Blissful Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Euphoric Collage Variations
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Ecstacy Collage
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Description: Collage Variations, White Objects on Reddish Background
    - Title: (Box 41)
      Number of Items: 253
  - Subseries G: Portrait
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 42)
      Description: Anderson, Laurie
      Number of Items: 153
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 42)
      Description: Anderson, Laurie with William Burroughs and John Giorno
    - Title:, 1983 (Box 42)
      Description: Anger, Kenneth
      Number of Items: 185
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 42)
      Description: Anger, Kenneth - boyfriend
    - Title: Astor, Patti, 1982 (Box 43)
      Number of Items: 464
    - Title: (Box 44)
      Description: Bagley, Darrell
    - Title:, 1984 (Box 44)
      Description: Bidlo, Mike
    - Title: (Box 44)
    - Title: (Box 44)
      Description: Burroughs, William
    - Title: (Box 44)
    - Title:, 1987 (Box 44)
      Description: Churicova, Inna
    - Title:, 1987 (Box 44)
      Description: Panvilov, Gleb
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 44)
      Description: Clarence / Greenwich
    - Title: (Box 44)
    - Title: (Box 44)
      Description: Cote, Thom
    - Title: (Box 44)
      Number of Items: 102
    - Title: (Box 44)
    - Title: (Box 45)
      Description: Danceteria Ad
      Number of Items: 212
    - Title: (Box 45)
    - Title: (Box 45)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy with Darrell Bagley and Jimmy Jr.
    - Title: (Box 45)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy with Jimmy Jr.
    - Title:, 1982 (Box 45)
      Description: de Sana, Jo
    - Title: (Box 45)
      Description: Derringer, Liz
    - Title: (Box 45)
      Description: Diode
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 45)
    - Title: (Box 45)
      Description: Gi Gi
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 45)
      Description: Giorno, John
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 46)
      Number of Items: 54
    - Title: (Box 46)
      Description: Harry, Debra
    - Title: (Box 46)
      Description: Hidalgo, Edwardo
    - Title: (Box 46)
    - Title: (Box 46)
      Description: Jerome - Model
      Number of Items: 155
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 46)
      Description: Lounge Lizards
    - Title: (Box 46)
      Description: Lovich, Lena
      Number of Items: 173
    - Title: (Box 47)
      Description: Mazey - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 47)
    - Title: (Box 47)
    - Title: (Box 47)
      Description: McCormick, Carlo and Tessa Hughes-Freeland Shoot
    - Title: (Box 47)
      Description: Hughes-Freeland, Tessa
    - Title: (Box 47)
    - Title: (Box 47)
      Description: Nylon, Judy
    - Title: (Box 47)
      Description: Phillips, Anya
    - Title: (Box 47)
      Description: Resnick, Marcia
    - Title: (Box 47)
      Description: Rosenblum-Kaplowitz, Jane with unidentified kids
    - Title:, 1985 (Box 47)
      Description: Scharf, Kenny
    - Title: (Box 47)
    - Title: (Box 47)
      Description: Sellers, Terence and Duncan Hannah
    - Title: (Box 48)
      Description: Simmons, Laurie
      Number of Items: 61
    - Title: (Box 48)
      Description: Simmons, Laurie - nephew, cowboy outfit
      Number of Items: 103
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 48)
      Number of Items: 84
    - Title: (Box 48)
      Description: Stefanotty, Robert
    - Title: (Box 48)
      Description: Sussler, Betsy
    - Title: (Box 48)
    - Title: (Box 48)
    - Title: (Box 48)
      Description: Victor Hugo (Halston’s boyfriend)
    - Title: (Box 48)
      Description: Warhol, Andy with Debra Harry, Jimmy de Sana, and Warhol star Victor Hugo
    - Title:, 1974 (Box 49)
      Description: Unidentified Face close-up
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 49)
      Description: Unidentified male nude at swimming pool
    - Title:, 1989 (Box 49)
      Description: Unidentified male subjects seated
    - Title: (Box 49)
      Description: "Unidentified man Red light"
    - Title: (Box 49)
      Description: Unidentified Nude male on roof
    - Title: (Box 49)
      Description: "Unknown Couple Beach"
    - Title: (Box 49)
      Description: Unknown Man
      Number of Items: 340
    - Title: (Box 49)
    - Title: (Box 49)
      Description: Unknown Couple
  - Subseries H: Other Artists' Work
    - Title: (Box 50)
      Description: Other Artists' Work
  - Subseries I: Travel
    - Title: (Box 50)
      Description: Travel
      Number of Items: 353
    - Title: (Box 51)
      Number of Items: 360
- Series V: Negatives by project
  Materials are organized chronologically by project. Within the subseries, individual frames are grouped by description; here, the number of items indicates the number of frames grouped under that same description. The negatives have been retained in the order found.
  - Subseries A: 101 Nudes
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Gail Nudeback shoot
      Process: Negative
      Number of Items: 171
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Byron Nude at 999”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Byron Nude"
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Mary Palmer model
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: "Cathy Simpson nude"
      Number of Items: 100
  - Subseries B: Submission
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Tube in Tub
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Shower / Rinse
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Shaving
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Dildo Mouth
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Enema #1 (Shit)
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Enema #1
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Scat #1
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Wax
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Enema on Carpet and Whip in Mouth
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Terrace with Cat
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Betty in Window
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Eggs / Refrigerator
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Fem Upside Down
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Fem with Chair
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Fem Piercing
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: RBR Shoulder and Shoes
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Toilet
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Clothes Pins
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Car Trunk
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Fem Strip
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Water Sports Tube
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Saluki
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Contact Paper and Cat toilet Bondage
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Terrace
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Jock Strap / Dildo Betty
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Water Sports / Bondage
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Ball Sep (Bed) / Torture
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Foot Fuck
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Scat #2
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Whip in Ass
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Ball Sex / Leaf
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Water Sports Tube (Terry’s)
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Penis Torture with Terry
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Masking Tape
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Giant Dildo
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Water Sports Kitchen
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: String Bondage on platform
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Shower Enema
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Fist Fuck
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Enema Carpet
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Auto Bondage
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Sofa Shackles
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Crucifix
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Transvestite theme
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: String Bondage
    - Title:, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
      Description: Fem Sofa Bondage
    - Title: (Box 52)
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “RBR, Sofa Heels”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “RBR, Coffee Table Heels”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “RBR, Trapped Sofa”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “RBR, Balanced Sofa”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Cigarette, Beach”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: "Condom Labeled by JDS “Contraceptive” "
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Eggs”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Foot Worship”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “TV”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Ball Crusher”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Mirror, Terry” Terence Sellers
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “7 Gates”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Strap on
    - Title: (Box 52)
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM
      Number of Items: 85
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM with Model
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM with Model #1
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: "Labeled by JDS SandM with Model #2 Whip "
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM #1
      Number of Items: 65
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM #2
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM #3
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM #4
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM #5
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM #6
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM #7
    - Title: (Box 52)